Guide to the Confederate Imprint collection, 1855-1879 MS 071
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Crandall Numbers; 1855-1867, 227678
  - Freemasons. Virginia. Richmond Lodge, No.10. By-Laws and list of members of Richmond Lodge, No.XIX, Ancient York Masons, 1864; 227688 (Box 15, Folder C5113)
  - Charleston Mercury Facsimile, April 14, 1861; 227687 (Box 15, Folder C5136)
  - The Commission--vol 6, no.1, 1861; 227686 (Box 15, Folder C5146)
  - The Southern Literary Messenger; devoted to Every Department of Literature, and the Fine Arts, Richmond, Va. Vol.36, no.38, vol.37,no.5 only, 1861-64; 227685 (Box 15, Folder C5266)
  - Southern Literary Messenger (addenda) vols 38:1 (incomplete, Jan. 1864), 38:4 (April, 1864), 38:5 (May, 1864; 2 copies), 33:5 (November, 1861), 1861-1864; 227684 (Box 15, Folder C5266)
  - The Southern Presbyterian Review. Columbia, SC V.14 No.3, October 1861; 227683 (Box 15, Folder C5270)
  - 14th New York Heavy Artillery Veteran Association 23rd Annual Reunion, n.d.; 227682 (Box 15, Folder N/A)
  - Civil War Senate Invitation, 186-; 227681 (Box 15, Folder N/A)
  - Civil War Honor Roll, n.d.; 227680 (Box 15, Folder N/A)
  - Confederate Fuse laid Under Water at Fort Fisher, North Carolina, with the intention of destroying forts and federal forces after capture, 1864; 227679 (Box 15, Folder N/A)
- Series X: Oversize, 227659
  - Daily Advertiser Extra!, April 2, 1865; 227677 (Box 16)
  - General Sherman's Campaign War Map, 186-; 227676 (Box 16)
  - United States Military Record: 137th Regiment O.V.P., 186-; 227675 (Box 16)
  - Census of Wisconsin from the year 1836 to August 1860, inclusive, 227674 (Box 16)
  - Public Acts, Private Acts, and Resolutions Passed at the 1859-60 Session of the Tennessee State Congress, 1860; 227673 (Box 16)
  - Published Letter from Washington Hunt Defending Against Accusations by Horace Greeley, July 25, 1860; 227672 (Box 16)
  - Broadside: N.C. Standard ---Extra. Supports W.W.Holden's candidacy for governor, July 12, 1864; 227671 (Box 16)
  - Proclamation by his Excellency, W.W.Holden, Raleigh, N.Y., January 30, 1869; 227670 (Box 16)
  - Advertisement Supporting Charles Brown for the Delaware Election, 186-; 227669 (Box 16)
  - Loyal Publication Society Union Broadside No.1, 1863; 227668 (Box 16)
  - The True Issue: What Leading Democrats and Conservatives Say, issed from the office of the Rebellion Record, 186?; 227667 (Box 16)
  - June 24, 1867, XXX; 227666 (Box 16, Folder Invitation to take part in ceremony of the Tammany Society, or Columbian Order)
  - Recruiting Advertisement for "The Excelsior Cavalry" under Edward E. Ropes, 1861; 227665 (Box 16)
  - Company I, Fifth Regiment, Mass. Volunteer Militia, Somerville Light Infantry Roster, April 20, 1861; 227664 (Box 16)
  - "The Seat of War" A Bird's Eye View of part of Maryland, District of Columbia, and part of Virginia, 227663 (Box 16)
  - Various Papers including "Freedom Paper" belonging to a slave, Appeal for Peace sent to Lieut. Gen.Scott, 1861, Public School Library Society of St. Louis, 1865, U.S. Sanitary Commission, 1865, Whitney Family Genealogy, 1879, Confederate Money, and Slave Bill of Sale, April 1849, 1849-1879; 227662 (Box 16)
  - Various Papers including Concert of War Songs, 1862, US Military Pass, 1861, Electoral Ticket for President of the Confederacy, Prison Bill of Fare by a prisoner of war, and Conditions of Peace required of the so-called seceded States, 1861-1865; 227661 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, LA. Jefferson Journal and unidentified photo of a man from same period, June 8, 1959; 227660 (Box 16)